After your sister took it
I shouldn't have immediately made excuses for her
About the West City Yunwan contract
your reminder was right on time
If you hadn't withdrawn the guarantee
the Su family might have faced huge risks
It's not that you don't care about the big picture
you just saw before we did
what the real big picture is
Mingyao
can you give
Mom and Dad another chance
I heard your apologies
and I accept them
But accepting your apologies doesn't mean
everything can go back to how it was
Mingyao
are you disowning us
No
You are my parents
That will never change
But from now on I'll decide my own marriage
and I'll decide my own career
My old belongings evidence and reputation
will no longer be used by anyone to keep the peace
As for the cooperation between the Su family and the Fu Group
if there's an opportunity in the future
it must go through formal procedures
Don't use me to test Fu Chenzhou
and don't use family ties to make
me ask favors for the Su family
The Fu Group won't let personal